<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Media List</string>
    <string name="title_movie_detail">Media Detail</string>


    <!--    CS315: DO THIS-->
    <!--    TODO: Create five NEW movie objects here. Complete with images and URLs. DELETE the two existing movies, they are only here as an example-->


    <string name="example_1_title">Generic Rom Com</string>
    <string name="example_1_description">Naturally, focuses on 2 people who really shouldn’t be together. It somehow becomes mutually advantageous for them to be together, or perhaps, they are interested in each other but their romance is based on false pretenses. Because the leads generally have no charisma, they each need a zany best friend who inserts dirty jokes wherever necessary. The two leads will fall in love in an extended music montage set to the music of Sixpence None the Richer. Once they find out about the false pretenses, they will take some time apart but realize how much they care for the other. Then comes “The Chase,” which can either be in an airport (not legal anymore), in traffic or somehow on boats. \n \nYou've seen this before, but not with these two actors!</string>
    <string name="example_1_year">2018</string>
    <string name="example_1_image">genericromcom</string>
    <string name="example_1_url">http://showtimeshowdown.com/5-cliche-formulas-of-movie-genres/</string>

    <string name="example_2_title">Every Action Movie Ever</string>
    <string name="example_2_description">The villain has left the hero for dead, or killed the hero’s brother, sister, parents, wife or family pets. Filled with righteous fury, the hero tools up and embarks on a bloody rampage.\n\nIf the movie does well, we will do it again in the sequel!\n\nMaybe the villain tries to get revenge on the hero for getting revenge on the villain in the next movie...</string>
    <string name="example_2_year">2019</string>
    <string name="example_2_image">genericaction</string>
    <string name="example_2_url">http://www.denofgeek.com/us/movies/18824/the-5-most-common-action-movie-plots</string>


</resources>
