<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Media List</string>
    <string name="title_movie_detail">Media Detail</string>


    <!--Rat Movie -->
    <string name="ratTitle">The Rat Movie</string>
    <string name="ratDescription">"In the middle of the night, The Rats and their leader The Giant Rat sing their legendary chant:
    Rats: Rats, we're rats, we're the rats. We prey at night, we stalk at night, we're the rats.
    Giant Rat: I'm da giant rat that makes all of da rules!
    Giant Rat and Rats: Let's see what kind of trouble we can get ourselves into﻿!"</string>
    <string name="ratYear">2014</string>
    <string name="ratImage">Thriller/Mystery</string>
    <string name="ratLink">https://jerma-lore.fandom.com/wiki/Rat_Movie</string>

    <!--Dead Poets Society -->
    <string name="poetTitle">Dead Poets Society</string>
    <string name="poetDescription">A new English teacher, John Keating (Robin Williams), is introduced to an all-boys preparatory school that
        is known for its ancient traditions and high standards. He uses unorthodox methods to reach out to his students, who face enormous
        pressures from their parents and the school. With Keating's help, students Neil Perry (Robert Sean Leonard), Todd Anderson (Ethan Hawke)
        and others learn to break out of their shells, pursue their dreams and seize the day.</string>
    <string name="poetYear">1989</string>
    <string name="poetImage">Dead Poet</string>
    <string name="poetLink">https://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/dead_poets_society</string>

    <!--Zathura -->
    <string name="zTitle">Zathura</string>
    <string name="zDescription">After their father (Tim Robbins) is called into work, two young boys, Walter (Josh Hutcherson)
            and Danny (Jonah Bobo), are left in the care of their teenage sister, Lisa (Kristen Stewart), and told they must stay inside. Walter
            and Danny, who anticipate a boring day, are shocked when they begin playing Zathura, a space-themed board game, which they realize
            has mystical powers when their house is shot into space. With the help of an astronaut (Dax Shepard), the boys attempt to return home.</string>
    <string name="zYear">2005</string>
    <string name="zImage">Zathura</string>
    <string name="zLink">https://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/zathura</string>

    <!--Inspector Gadget -->
    <string name="gadTitle">Inspector Gadget</string>
    <string name="gadDescription">John Brown (Matthew Broderick) is a bumbling but well-intentioned security guard who is badly injured
            in an explosion planned by an evil mastermind. He is taken to a laboratory, where Brenda (Joely Fisher), a leading robotics surgeon, replaces
            his damaged limbs with state-of-the-art gadgets and tools. Named Inspector Gadget by the press, John -- along with his niece, Penny
            (Michelle Trachtenberg), and her trusty dog, Brain -- uses his new powers to discover who was behind the explosion.</string>
    <string name="gadYear">1999</string>
    <string name="gadImage">Gadget</string>
    <string name="gadLink">https://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/inspector_gadget</string>

    <!--La La Land -->
    <string name="laTitle">La La Land</string>
    <string name="laDescription">Sebastian (Ryan Gosling) and Mia (Emma Stone) are drawn together by their common desire
            to do what they love. But as success mounts they are faced with decisions that begin to fray the fragile fabric of their love
            affair, and the dreams they worked so hard to maintain in each other threaten to rip them apart.</string>
    <string name="laYear">2016</string>
    <string name="laImage">La La</string>
    <string name="laLink">https://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/la_la_land</string>
    <string name="title_activity_launch">launch</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading</string>


</resources>
